Today we're going to learn how to make our own hoop earrings.
Of course, you can buy a hoop.
They sell them in craft stores and they look very similar to this.
As you can see, the form is very simple and we can do it on our own for free.
We're going to take a inch and a half to 2 inches piece of wire.
It's got to be a strong wire.
Not one that's going to bend really easily.
You're going to grab the piece of wire at the very end.
This time, you're probably going to make a medium size loop.
Using that same wrist turning method, you're going to bring the wire just till the end touches your main part of the wire.
You may even want to straighten that out a bit using your pliers.
Now, to make it in a curve shape, you can either curve it around something that is round if you have issues with the shape, or you can just kind of grab your wire and keep twisting to make that circular shape.
When you're finished, you'll have a hoop shape much like this.